questions:
  - question: "List the available commands that correspond to alpha features."
    solution: "kubectl alpha"
  - question: "Add or update the annotations of one or more resources."
    solution: "kubectl annotate"
  - question: "List the API resources that are available."
    solution: "kubectl api-resources"
  - question: "List the API versions that are available."
    solution: "kubectl api-versions"
  - question: "Apply a configuration change to a resource from a file or stdin."
    solution: "kubectl apply"
  - question: "Attach to a running container."
    solution: "kubectl attach"
  - question: "Inspect authorization."
    solution: "kubectl auth"
  - question: "Automatically scale the set of pods managed by a replication controller."
    solution: "kubectl autoscale"
  - question: "Modify certificate resources."
    solution: "kubectl certificate"
  - question: "Display endpoint information about the master and services in the cluster."
    solution: "kubectl cluster-info"
  - question: "Output shell completion code for the specified shell (bash or zsh)."
    solution: "kubectl completion"
  - question: "Modify kubeconfig files."
    solution: "kubectl config"
  - question: "Convert config files between different API versions."
    solution: "kubectl convert"
  - question: "Mark node as unschedulable."
    solution: "kubectl cordon"
  - question: "Copy files and directories to and from containers."
    solution: "kubectl cp"
  - question: "Create one or more resources from a file or stdin."
    solution: "kubectl create"
  - question: "Delete resources from a file, stdin, or by selectors."
    solution: "kubectl delete"
  - question: "Display the detailed state of one or more resources."
    solution: "kubectl describe"
  - question: "Diff file or stdin against live configuration."
    solution: "kubectl diff"
  - question: "Drain node in preparation for maintenance."
    solution: "kubectl drain"
  - question: "Edit a resource on the server."
    solution: "kubectl edit"
  - question: "List events."
    solution: "kubectl events"
  - question: "Execute a command against a container in a pod."
    solution: "kubectl exec"
  - question: "Get documentation for a resource."
    solution: "kubectl explain"
  - question: "Expose a resource as a new Kubernetes service."
    solution: "kubectl expose"
  - question: "List one or more resources."
    solution: "kubectl get"
  - question: "Build a set of Kustomize resources."
    solution: "kubectl kustomize"
  - question: "Add or update the labels of one or more resources."
    solution: "kubectl label"
  - question: "Print the logs for a container in a pod."
    solution: "kubectl logs"
  - question: "List global command-line options."
    solution: "kubectl options"
  - question: "Update one or more fields of a resource."
    solution: "kubectl patch"
  - question: "Provides utilities for interacting with plugins."
    solution: "kubectl plugin"
  - question: "Forward one or more local ports to a pod."
    solution: "kubectl port-forward"
  - question: "Run a proxy to the Kubernetes API server."
    solution: "kubectl proxy"
  - question: "Replace a resource from a file or stdin."
    solution: "kubectl replace"
  - question: "Manage the rollout of a resource."
    solution: "kubectl rollout"
  - question: "Run a specified image on the cluster."
    solution: "kubectl run"
  - question: "Update the size of a replication controller."
    solution: "kubectl scale"
  - question: "Configure application resources."
    solution: "kubectl set"
  - question: "Update the taints on one or more nodes."
    solution: "kubectl taint"
  - question: "Display resource usage of pods or nodes."
    solution: "kubectl top"
  - question: "Mark node as schedulable."
    solution: "kubectl uncordon"
  - question: "Display the Kubernetes version."
    solution: "kubectl version"
  - question: "Wait for a specific condition on one or many resources."
    solution: "kubectl wait"
